I sell business training to business clients.
So last year we did 14.8 million.
Bad ass, what do you teach them how to do?
Teach them how to grow their business.
Is it courses that are done in person or is it digital?
We have the in-person model
and we want to scale to 25 million,
run 12 to 15 live in-person events on a monthly basis,
which are three events.
Right now who's doing the pitching at the events?
So I've got about six to eight people that I've trained
and we've got some really good ones,
but it does take a long time to get those people
up to speed to be able to do a really good job.
Well, let me ask you a question about the pitching.
So when you have the pitch, is there a slide deck?
Yeah, yeah.
How many slides is it?
268 for the day.
Yeah, yeah, for the whole day?
Yeah, for the day.
Ah, all right.
So let me just make your life a hundred times easier
for six days of work.
So the pitch should be word for word scripted on the slides.
So my pitch at Money Models, the book launch,
was 1,700 slides just for the 90 minute presentation
that I gave, which means every word I said
was on the screen paired with a visual
for people who don't speak English that good.
The only thing that you need to train them on
is how fast to say the words, how loudly to say it,
when to raise their voice and when to lower it
and what to do with their hands.